# JENNIFER ARBOLEDA

Chicago, IL | (773) 849-2761 | arboleda.jen@gmail.com | linkedin.com/jennifer-arboleda

#### PERFORMANCE MANAGEMENT SPECIALIST

Creative and tech-savvy **performance manager** with a Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) in Communication, Media, and Theater. Background in product marketing and brand promoting. Comfortability in customer service and problem-solving lead to quick promotion to Senior level role. **Areas of expertise include:** 

## RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

### CARS.COM, September 2019 – Present

*In-Market Video Performance Manager* – Chicago, IL December 2021 – Present

- Maintain Cars.com's largest group sized accounts
- Utilizes Google Suite, Google Analytics, Google Data Studio, proprietary data, and Tableau reports to track KPI's, provide user insights, and suggest data driven adjustments to the client's current creative and marketing campaigns.
- Created Performance Management team's new hire process, new hire training, training checklist, and several curriculums. Led multiple group trainings, including cross-departmental initiatives with leadership.

Senior Account Executive – Chicago, IL September 2019 – November 2021

- Maintain relationship and drive revenue of 150+ car dealerships worth ~\$1.9M annually
- Sell products and services to existing customers and prospects via multiple mediums (e.g., phone, chat, email, video conferencing, etc.).
- Respond to client inquiries and offer guidance on appropriate products and services that will address their business' pain points and goals
- Provide insight to customers, identify and close upsell opportunities.
- Created and executed a Pilot Program aimed at helping team members better service their customers, problem solve, and develop successful talk tracks
- Serve as sole Spanish-speaking AE and assist the inside team as a whole in servicing and upselling to this customer base

## WYZANT, INC., October 2018 – September 2019

Customer Support Representative - Chicago, IL

- Pioneered a project which focused on collecting, reviewing, and categorizing 3,500 tickets.
- AAE: Copy editing of material and data entry
- TCTPP: Event planning, inventory ordering, and leading cultural initiatives for our department, proposal drafting, budgeting
- Part of a selective Profile Review Team Investigation of delinquent accounts.

EDUCATION	ACTIVITIES	HONORS
Northeastern Illinois University BA: Communication, Media, and Theater	Mi Gente, 2020 to Present  Board Member, Communications Chair – Chicago, IL	<b>cum laude</b> , 2018 Northeastern Illinois University
May 2018 – Chicago, IL	<ul> <li>Member and leader in Employee Resource Group.</li> <li>Started this group with Latinx colleagues to increase</li> </ul>	2018 – Chicago, IL
Harold Washington College  AA: Communication	visibility and support for the Latinx community within the CARS organization.	
December 2015 – Chicago, IL	CitySquash, 2003 to Present	
	Team Member - Bronx, NY	
	<ul> <li>Member of selective urban squash and enrichment program with a focus on squash, academics, mentoring, community service, and travel.</li> </ul>	